motachashma.com 2018-01-22

# Privacy Policy | Mota Chashma

At [Motachashma.com](http://www.motachashma.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by the website [Motachashma.com](http://www.motachashma.com/) and how it is used. The Privacy Policy applies to the Site, as well as all products and services offered by Mota Chashma 

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users/ Visitors in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers’ utilized and other similar information. 

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

Mota Chashma may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve customer service- Information you provide help us respond to your customer service requests and support your needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience-We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site-We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * To process payments-We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails-If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, [Motachashma.com](http://www.motachashma.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

The Site does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. The “Cookies” are used to enhance User Experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [Motachashma.com](http://www.motachashma.com/).
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.motachashma.com](http://www.motachashma.com/) and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

## Third Party Website

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners may include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on motachashma.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Mota Chashma has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Mota Chashma’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

## Changes to this privacy policy

Mota Chashma has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

## Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Motachashma  
492, Avas Vikas , Roorkee, Dist- Haridwar, Uttarakhand - 247667  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@motachashma.com   
Last updated at : June 01, 2014
